{
  "name": "Leopardy Trivia Board",
  "categories": ["Informatica", "Geografia", "Letteratura", "Storia", "Scienza"],
  "rows": [
    {
      "points": "Points 100",
      "questions": [
        { "question": "SW4gd2hpY2ggeWVhciB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IFByb2dyYW1tYWJsZSBsYW5ndWFnZSBjcmVhdGVkPw==", "answer": "MTk0OQ==" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgY2FwaXRhbCBvZiBGcmFuY2U/", "answer": "UGFyaXM=" },
        { "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJUaGUgRGl2aW5lIENvbWVkeSI/", "answer": "RGFudGVBbcOp" },
        { "question": "V2hpY2ggYW5jaWVudCBjaXZpbGl6YXRpb24gbWFya2VkIHRoZSBlbmQgb2YgdGhlIFJvbWFuIFJlcHVibGljPw==", "answer": "NDc0IEFE" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc2NpZW50aWZpYyBuYW1lIGZvciB0aGUgc3R1ZHkgb2YgbGlmZSBhbmQgdGhlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBvZiBsaXZpbmcgb3JnYW5pc21zPw==", "answer": "QmlvbG9neQ==" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "Points 175",
      "questions": [
        { "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIFRDUCBzdGFuZCBmb3I/", "answer": "VHJhbnNtaXNzaW9uIENvbnRyb2wgUHJvdG9jb2w=" },
        { "question": "V2hpY2ggU291dGggQW1lcmljYW4gY291bnRyeSBpcyB0aGUgbGFyZ2VzdCBieSBsYW5kIGFyZWE/", "answer": "QnJhemls" },
        { "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJUaGUgQnJvdGhlcnMiPw==", "answer": "S2FmayBhbmQgVGhlIEtldHRsZQ==" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgYSBjaGFyYWN0ZXJpc3RpYyBvZiBSb21hbiBlbXBpcm9ycyBhbmQgd2FzIGFuIGF1dGhvciBvZiB0aGUgQWVuZWlkPw==", "answer": "VmlyZ2ls" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3R1ZHkgb2YgdGhlIHN0cnVjdHVyYWwgcHJvcGVydGllcyBvZiBtYXRlcmlhbHM/", "answer": "TWVjaGFuaWNz" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "Points 350",
      "questions": [
        { "question": "V2hpY2ggYWxnb3JpdGhtIHVzZXMgYSByZWN1cnNpdmUgcHJvY2VkcmFsIGFuZCBmZWF0dXJlcyBhIHN0YWNrIGJhc2VkIG1lbW9yeQ==", "answer": "U3BvcmV0" },
        { "question": "V2hpY2ggU2VhIGhhcyB0aGUgZGVlcGVzdCBwb2ludCBpbiB0aGUgd29ybGQ/", "answer": "TWFyaWFuYSBUcmVuY2g=" },
        { "question": "V2hvIHdyb3RlICJNYWMgdGhlIE51bnRoaW5nIg==", "answer": "SmFtZXMgSm95Y2U=" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IG1ham9yIGVtcGlyZSBvZiB0aGUgU3BhbmlzaCBFbXBpcmU/", "answer": "Q2hhcmxlbWFnbmU=" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgcGFydCBvZiBhIGNlbGwgdGhhdCBjb250YWlucyB0aGUgZ2VuZXRpYyBtYXRlcmlhbCBuZWVkZWQgdG8gcHJvZHVjZSBwcmlvdGVpbnM/", "answer": "TnVjbGV1cw==" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "points": "Points 500",
      "questions": [
        { "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgdHdvLWxldHRlciBjb2RlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFVuaWNvZGUgc3RhbmRhcmQ/", "answer": "VVROLTE2" },
        { "question": "V2hpY2ggY29udGluZW50IHNlcGFyYXRlcyBFdXJhc2lhIGFuZCBBZnJpY2E/", "answer": "VGhlIE1lZGl0ZXJyYW5lYW4gU2Vh" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgY2hhcmFjdGVyIHdobyBjcmVhdGVkIFNoZXJsb2NrIEhvbG1lcz8=", "answer": "QXJ0aHVyIENvbmFuIERveWxl" },
        { "question": "V2hhdCBiYXR0bGUgaW5jbHVkZWQgdGhlIGZhbW91cyBCYXR0bGUgb2YgdGhlIFJpdmVyIFBsYXRlYW5zPw==", "answer": "VGhlIEJhdHRsZSBvZiBXYXRlcmxvbw==" },
        { "question": "V2hpY2ggZm9yY2UgZGV0ZXJtaW5lcyB0aGUgbW90aW9uIG9mIGFuIGVsZWN0cm9uPyA=", "answer": "TG9yZW56IEZvcmNl" }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
